24小时
第三季  第六集
前情提要
欢迎参加总统大卫·帕默尔和议员约翰 基勒
Welcome to the first of three debates between President David Palmer,
的总统竞选辩论的首场
and Senator John Keeler.
我属下刚刚了解到
My office has just learned,
近来与总统交往的女人:安妮 帕卡德医生
that the woman with whom the President is currently involved: Dr. Anne Packard
正由于伪造临床药检结果而被指控
is being accused of helping to fabricate the results of a clinical drug trial.
总统是否对这些指控充耳不闻?
Did the President know of these accusations and choose to ignore them?
金 你父亲试图劫走萨拉扎 你上一次联系他是什么时候?
Kim, your dad's trying to break out Salazar. When's the last time you heard from him?
半小时前 他要我发出拉姆·萨拉扎的转移指令
About half an hour ago. He asked me to issue a transfer order for Ramon Salazar.
-而你照办了?  -对啊 他说萨拉扎需要被转移
-And you did it?  -Yeah, he said that Salazar needed to be moved.
-而你现在告诉我没这回事  -对 金很抱歉但是你父亲对你撒谎了
-But now you're telling me this isn't true.  -No Kim, I'm sorry your dad lied to you.
他会怎么样?
What's gonna happen to him?
最理想的解决办法是找到凯尔 辛格勒
The best way out of this whole situation is to find Kyle Singer.
这样你父亲就会交出萨拉扎
Then your dad'll give up Salazar.
你在做什么? 出不去的
What are you doing? There is no way out of here.
如果我死了 病毒也会随我而去
If I die, the virus is dying with me.
等等! 别!
Wait! No!
找到了 一辆巡逻车找到了载凯尔 辛格勒的货车
I got it, a patrol car just found the truck Kyle Singer was in.
通知待命小队
Hype this into the teams on stand-by.
在场人员皆有可能为病毒携带者 根据疾控中心一级协议行动
Assume everyone on site is contagious and use level 1 CDC protocol.
如果要我搞定现状 你得信任我
If I get out of this thing, you're gonna have to trust me.
-蔡斯!  -你在干什么 杰克?
-Chase!  -What are you doing Jack?
我得在60秒内将萨拉扎送上那架直升机
I've got to get Salazar in the air in that chopper in the next 60 seconds
不然成千上万的人会死去 你选吧
or a hundred thousand of people will die. You choose.
这里是典狱官 米切尔我要所有部队退下
This is Warden Mithell, I want all teams to stand down, I repeat, stand down!
祝贺
Congratulations!
你现在是比我更出名的国家公敌了
Now you are an even bigger enemy to your country than I am.
我们有足够的油去墨西哥么?
Do we have enough fuel to get to Mexico?
-我们不是前往墨西哥  -什么意思? 为什么不去?
-We're not going to Mexico.  -What do you mean? Why not?
如果我们试图穿越边境 他们会尝试让我们迫降
If we make a run for the border, they'll just try and force us down.
你得相信我
You're gonna have to trust me.
-作战部 奥布莱恩?  -克萝伊 我是蔡斯
-Field office, O'Brian?  -Chloe, it's Chase.
杰克拆掉了定位器 不过军方应该在雷达上找到他了
Jack disarmed his locator but the military should have him on radar by now.
他们正给我们提供数据 蔡斯 我现在就发给你
They're feeding us the stream now Chase, I'm sending it to you.
他刚刚改道
He just banked.
-他正向西 前往市中心  -市中心
-He's heading west towards downtown.  -Downtown.
他知道他们在人口密集区不能开火
He knows they can't shoot him down over a populated area.
我们没准能绕过他的通讯设置 通过紧急频带
We may be able to override what he did to his com unit through an emergency hailing frequency.
我们必须联系上他克萝伊
We have to get through to him Chloe.
-我们得告诉他 凯尔 辛格勒已经找到  -明白
-We gotta let him know we found Kyle Singer.  -On it.
布兰卡德少校 我是瑞恩·查佩尔 你属下的追击部队情况如何
Major Blanchard, this is Ryan Chappelle, what's the status of your pursuit craft?
我这儿有两架直升机刚刚起飞
I have 2 helicopters that have just taken off from down here.
-什么时候他们会遭遇?  -情况刚改变
-How quickly will they intercept?  -Well that's changed.
鲍尔 刚转向 他不朝我们这边飞了
Bauer just turned, he's no longer heading south toward us.
他在向哪儿飞?
Where is he heading?
看起来他正朝着城市去
Looks like he's heading towards the city
以他现在的速度 10分钟内我们进入射程范围
At he's current speed it will take us 10 minutes before we get within range.
你必须强迫他降落 如有必要可以将其击落
You go to force him down, even shoot him down if it comes to that.
但是一旦他进入城市 我们这么做将无法避免机坠事故
But we can't do that while he's over the city without incurring serious collateral damage.
那你得在他抵达城市前 一旦着陆 他们会逃之夭夭
Then you have to do it before he gets to the city, if he lands, they'll be difficult to catch.
-是  -保证此线路通畅
-Yes, sir.  -Keep this line open.
米歇尔 我现在替代托尼 局里要求一位高级官员管理反恐局
Michelle, I'm taking over for Tony, Division wants a senior officer in charge of CTU.
给我最新消息
Give me an update.
我们正试图和直升机联系
We're trying to make contact with the Chopper.
我们已经找到了凯尔 辛格勒 而病毒也被隔离 我们得联系杰克
Now that we have Kyle Singer and the virus has been contained, we need to contact Jack,
告诉他 帮助萨拉扎逃离已无关紧要
let him know that the attempted escape of Salazar is pointless.
那么 把部门主管都叫到会议室 我要所有人都统一行动
Ok, assemble all the department heads in the conference area, I want everyone on the same page.
那么C频带呢?
What about C-Band?
那是架特种直升机 他们不会用那些频率
It's a SWAT chopper. They wouldn't be using those frequencies.
亚当 把你手头的搁一下 2分钟内我们要到会议室听简报
Adam, tie up whatever you're doing, we have a briefing in the conference area in two.
金 过来
Kim, over here.
有什么要帮忙的?
What do you need?
我要你在克萝伊找直升机的频道时 帮她整理这列表
I need you to anchor this list for Chloe, while she is trying to find an admitting channel for the Chopper.
知道了
I'm on it.
-抱歉 我把那件东西落在你父亲的办公室了  -没关系
-Sorry, I lost it in your dad's office.  -It's ok.
你告诉米歇尔找到的麻药了么?
Did you tell Michelle about the drug you found in there?
是的
Yeah.
-他们准备怎么做?  -我不知道
-What are they gonna do?  -I don't know.
发生了太多事 没人有时间管这个
Everything came in right after that so no one has had time to process.
-把头两组发给我  -好
-Send me the first 2 groups.  -Sure.
我们会竭尽全力联系杰克让此事安全解决
We'll make every attempt to communicate with Jack, trying to resolve this peacefully.
但是如果我们失败了 我要每个人清楚
But if we can't, I need everyone absolutely clear on this.
萨拉扎的恐怖组织对我国造成严重威胁
Salazar's terrorist connections are a serious threat to this country.
我们不能看着他跑了
We cannot let him leave.
现在我们找到了辛格勒 因此
Now that we've got Singer, should it come to it,
萨拉扎和鲍尔都是弃子
both Salazar and Bauer are expandable.
为什么我们不集中精力想办法 让直升机安全着陆?
Why aren't we focusing on other options that would bring down the Chopper without force.
杰克并不给我们机会
Jack is not giving us any options.
无论结果如何 他都必死无疑
He's on a suicide mission either way.
一旦他把拉姆交给赫克托 他们就会卸磨杀驴
Once he hands Ramon off to Hector, they'll have no use for him, they're going to kill him.
我刚刚收到布兰卡德少校的电话
I just got off the phone with Major Blanchard.
他的部队正在追击杰克
He has pursuit crafts tracking Jack.
如果他们无法在他逃入人群前 抓住他
However if they're not able to catch him by the time he reaches his metro airspace
那么我们就有一堆新麻烦了
then we have an all new set of problems.
我们必须现在联系当地警局
We need to coordinate with local authorities now.
赫克托 放轻松
Hector, relax.
为什么我联系不上盖尔?
Why can't I reach Gael?
他走不脱身
He can't get away.
我必须立刻了解拉姆的情况
I need to know what's going on with Ramon now!
政府大概正在释放他 只是需要时间
The Government is probably releasing him, it's just taking some time.
他们并不是释放他
They're not releasing him.
-我并不想告诉你这个  -告诉我什么?
-I didn't want to tell you.  -Tell me what?
计划改变了 是杰克·鲍尔送拉姆出来
The plan has changed, Jack Bauer is the one who's going to deliver Ramon.
什么? 说笑吧?
What is that? A joke?
-不  -但这怎么可能?
-No.  -But how is that possible?
拉姆永远不会接受抓他的人的帮助
I mean Ramon will never accept help from the man who put him in prison.
不 他正在接受他的帮助
Oh no, he is accepting his help.
鲍尔 因此正被他祖国通缉
Bauer, is now a criminal in his own country for doing this.
赫克托 到底怎么回事?
Hector, what's going on?
你怎么能让鲍尔来找我们? 那太危险了
How could you let Bauer come to us, that's too dangerous.
-别担心 克劳迪娅  -不 我很担心
-Don't worry about it Claudia.  -No I am worried.
看看他对我们做了什么 这难道不是某种阴谋么?
Look what he's already done to us, is that some kind of trick?
别担心杰克·鲍尔 我自有办法对付他
Don't worry about Jack Bauer, I have plans for him.
喂?
Yes?
我没多少时间 我们正为此忙着
I don't have a lot of time, we're in the middle of this.
-拉姆还活着么?  -是的 他和鲍尔已经搭直升机逃脱了
-Is Ramon alive?  -Yes, he and Bauer have escaped in a helicopter.
-他们联系飞行员了么?  -没 他们正被追击
-Have they contacted their pilot yet?  -No, no, no, they're being pursued.
几分钟内定成败
Everything will be decided in the next few minutes.
查佩尔在作战会议时说了什么?
Hey, what did Chappelle say in the briefing?
他说了很多
He said a lot of stuff.
-他们会击落我父亲么?  -如果他们必须的话
-Are they gonna try and shoot at my father?  -If they have to, yeah.
但是如果他们能联系到你父亲 这就不会发生
But if they can contact him first, it won't come to that.
-克萝伊 你这里怎么样了?  -呼叫频率还是没反应
-Chloe, where are you at?  -No progress on the hailing frequency.
没有呼叫频率 我们联系不到他
Without that we can't get through to Jack.
好吧 试试这些新的 用恃索 我们得联系上那直升机
Ok, here some new ones to try, use a tree search, we gotta get through that chopper.
-金?  -在
-Kim?  -Yeah?
-我得和你谈谈  -好
-I need to speak to you.  -Sure.
瑞恩和我认为 在你爸的事解决前 你不适合留在这儿
Ryan and I feel you shouldn't be here, until the situation with your father is resolved.
-我能够胜任我的工作 米歇尔  -你能否胜任不是问题所在
-I'm qualified to handle the work, Michelle.  -Your qualifications are not an issue.
-你的感情是  -我能控制我的感情
-Your emotions are.  -I can control my emotions.
我父亲这么做是为了阻止病毒流散
My father is doing this so the virus won't get out.
如果他知道凯尔 辛格勒已经被抓 他会把萨拉扎送回来的
If he knows that Kyle Singer is in custody, he'll give Salazar back.
我知道 但是我们联系不上你父亲
I know but we can't reach your father.
现在不行 但是克萝伊和亚当正在努力 而我可以帮忙
Not yet, but Chloe and Adam are getting there, and I can help them.
我是有用的 米歇尔 别这样
I'm a resource Michelle, don't do this.
好吧 去帮他们吧
Ok, go back and help them.
如果我们必须打下那直升机 我要她离开这儿
If we have to fire on that chopper, I want her out of here.
怎么了?
What's going on?
-是军队  -你怎么知道
-It's military.  -How can you tell?
他们的阵型 他们的速度 3到4分钟内它们会赶上我们
Their formation, their range of speed, they're gonna be on us in the next 3 to 4 minutes.
然后?
And then what?
一旦他们追上 他们就会干掉我们
As soon they got on us, they shoot us out of the sky.
查佩尔?
Chappelle?
我刚和反恐局的人说过 他们说你授权攻击那直升机
I just spoke with someone at CTU, they said you authorize to use the force against the chopper.
没错 蔡斯
That's right Chase, I did.
总统帕默尔知道么?
Does President Palmer know about this?
帕默尔? 首先他正在参加竞选辩论
Palmer? First of all he's in the middle of a national debate.
而且我不需要他的许可
And I don't need his authorization.
鲍尔 刚帮拉姆·萨拉扎脱狱
Bauer just help Ramon Salazar break out of prison.
他这么做是为了确保 萨拉扎的人不释放病毒
He did that to make sure Salazar's people don't release the virus.
与我无关 这是我的管辖权
I don't care, but this is my jurisdiction.
我只是说得到帕默尔的许可
All I'm saying is that getting Palmer's authorization,
再行动会比较明智 好好想想
might be the smart play here. Think about it.
杰克·鲍尔和总统的关系不同寻常
Jack Bauer has a personal relationship with the President.
他救了总统不止一次
He saved his life more than once.
帕默尔曾经为他而破例
Palmer has interceded on his behalf before.
我们的职责不能对个人感情妥协
Our mandate does not bend to accommodate personal relationships.
一点没错瑞恩 等你把杰克打下来后 你就这么向总统解释吧
You're right Ryan. And after you shoot Jack down you can personally explain that to the President.
我是查佩尔?
Chappelle?
我们的飞机马上就能看见鲍尔了
Our aircrafts are about to make visual contact with Bauer.
-我们已经准备好开火而且...  -不要开火
-We can be ready to fire and...  -Do not fire!
重复 没有我的命令不要开火
Repeat, do not fire until you hear back from me.
总统曾许诺 对美国工人予以政策支持
The President has spoken of his administration support for the American worker,
但对加尔维斯顿市的阿曼德·罗德里格
but I'm sure these words sounds hollow to Armando Rodriguez of Galveston,
比洛克西市的肖恩·布朗
Sean Brown of Baloxi,
坦帕市的肯德尔·泰勒
to Kendall Taylor of Tampa,
以及成百上千 因总统签订了贸易协定 而失业的人来说
and to a hundred thousand of their fellow workers who have lost their jobs,
你的许诺只是空头大话
because of trade agreement signed by President David Palmer.
-韦恩·帕默尔  -帕默尔先生 我是瑞恩·查佩尔
-Wayne Palmer.  -Mr. Palmer, Ryan Chappelle call.
查佩尔先生 生化危机的情况怎么样了?
Mr. Chappelle what's the latest on the bio-threat?
我们认定的唯一病毒携带者 凯尔 辛格勒 已经被拘捕了
Kyle Singer, who we believe to be the only carrier of the virus has been taken in a custody.
你是说此病毒的扩散危机已经解除了?
Do you tell me there is no longer a risk of this virus being released?
-正是如此  -谢天谢地!
-That's what I'm saying.  -Oh thank God!
但是我们依旧得面对鲍尔的问题
Yes, we still have the Bauer situation to deal with.
他怎么了?
What's the status on that?
鲍尔正带着萨拉扎坐直升机逃亡
Bauer is taking Salazar from the prison in an helicopter,
我们有人在现场 但是无法取得联系
We have our men on site, but we aren't able to communicate with.
那么你准备怎么做?
So, what do you plan on doing?
萨拉扎不能离境
Salazar can't be allowed to leave the country.
我担心唯一的方法就是把他击落
I'm afraid our only alternative is to shoot him down.
查佩尔先生 我兄弟不会喜欢这个选择
Mr. Chappelle, my brother is not gonna like that alternative.
我明白 这就是我打来的原因
I understand, that's why I'm calling.
我不想没有总统的许可就开火
I don't want to fire on Bauer without the President permission.
是的 总统现在正参加竞选辩论直播
Yeah, well the President is in the middle of televised debate right now,
-我很抱歉 但是这得等  -不能等
-so I'm sorry but this is gonna have to wait.  -It can't wait.
几分钟内 他们的直升机就会抵达洛杉矶市中心
In a few minutes, their helicopter's going to be over downtown LA,
那时再开火 势必造成严重平民伤亡
and we will be unable to shoot it down without risking significant civilian casualties.
-我会再给你联系的 好么?  -尽快 帕默尔先生
-I'm gonna get back to you alright?  -Soon Mr. Palmer.
不然直升机着陆后 鲍尔和萨拉扎就会消失的无影无踪
Otherwise Bauer will be able to land that chopper and disappear with Salazar into the population.
明白
Yeah.
参议员基勒发言
Senator Keeler.
哪个经济专家? 内阁?
Who's the economic experts? The administrations?
我以及广大劳动者 不能接受
I, for one, cannot accept the blurred numbers
你内阁中所谓经济专家 编造的模糊数字
being projected, by the so called economic experts of this administration.
大卫 是我 生化危机已经解除
David it's me, the biological threat has been eliminated
我们已经拘留凯尔 辛格勒
We have Kyle Singer in custody.
然而 杰克·鲍尔并不知道 目前他正协助萨拉扎逃脱
However Jack Bauer doesn't know this and now he is facilitating Salazar escape.
他们坐的直升机正在城市外
and they're in a chopper in the outskirts of the city.
下面听好了 大卫
Now listen to me carefully David.
也许必须把他击落
It may be necessary to shoot him down.
我想听总统对于此问的回答
I would like to hear the President answer to that question.
你准备许可开火么?
Are you prepared to authorize this?
总统先生 您的回答
Mr. President, your response.
快点 大卫 你打算怎么样?
Come on David, what do you want to do?
我觉得整个美国劳力大军想听他的回答
I think the entire American work force would like to hear his answer.
总统先生?
Mr. President?
我亲爱的美国人民
My fellow Americans,
我刚收到一份需要我关注的国家警报
I have just been informed of an impending national emergency that requires my immediate attention.
因此 我必须从这场辩论中退出
Therefore I must withdraw from this debate.
抱歉
Excuse me.
这算什么?
Now what is this?
这是超乎想象的发展
This is to say the least an unusual situation.
给我清空这房间
I need this room cleared.
让这些人滚出去!!!
Get this people out of here!!!
救命!
Help!
你们带我去哪儿?
Where they're taking me?
Where do you taking me?
为什么你们都不说话?
Why don't you talk to me?
嗨! 你们干什么?
Hey! What are you doing?
你们去哪儿?
Where are you going?
到底发生什么?
What's going on?
-和我说话! 求你们了!  -凯尔 我是邓肯医生
-Talk to me! Please!  -Kyle, I'm doctor Duncan.
-我希望你冷静下来  -我的女朋友在哪儿?
-I need you to calm down.  -Where is my girl friend?
琳达 在哪儿?
Where is Linda?
我们把她带到了设施的另一部分
We have here in another part of the facility.
-她还好么?  -是的 她还好
-Is she ok?  -Yes, she is fine.
有14小时的潜伏期
There's an incubation period of 14 hours.
对于这种特殊的病毒 如果你还没有显现症状
With this particular virus if you haven't become symptomatic,
你就不会传染
You haven't transmitted it.
那我的父母呢?
And my parents?
-他们也不会有事?  -对
-They will be ok too?  -Yeah.
他们正在赶来
They're on their way.
万一我出现了症状
What happens when I do become
会怎么样?
symptomatic?
这像埃博拉一样是吧?(埃博拉:埃博拉出血热,有很高的死亡率)
It's like that Ebola thing, isn't it?
这病毒会把我生吞活剥吧?
It's gonna eat me alive?
我们会尽量让你没有痛苦的
We'll keep you has comfortable has possible.
阿尔法 1 斑马 1 我们已经可以目击
Alpha 1, Zebra 1, we have visual.
他们追上来了 已经锁定了我们的热能信号
They've got us. They've locked onto our heat signature.
-那为什么他们不开火?  -我不知道
-Then, why aren't they firing?  -I don't know.
克萝伊! 快 帮我接通呼叫频道!
Chloe! Come one, give me the hailing frequency!
我没法让服务器更快了
I can't make the servers go any faster, OK!
查佩尔先生 我们已经锁定直升机了
Mr. Chappelle we've just locked on to the chopper.
它还没有抵达人口密集区 我现在要回答
It is not yet over a populated zone. I need an answer.
准确来说我们还有多久?
How much time do we have precisely?
在坠落会造成重大伤亡前 我们还有4分钟
Before collateral damage becomes an issue, Mr., we've 4 minutes.
继续待命少校 我正在等总统的答复
Stay on course Major, I'm waiting to hear back from the President.
我们依旧没有获得任何有关国家警报的征兆
We still haven't got any indication as to the nature of this national emergency.
而议员基勒的属下正在追问此警报是否属实
And Senator Keeler's staff is questioning whether or not this emergency actually exists.
如果这真是国家警报 这出现的未免过于恰到好处
If this indeed is a national emergency of any sort, it would challenge the nation at this critical time.
能让我们私下谈谈么?
Could you give us a moment please?
大卫 很抱歉 但是我们没时间了
David, I'm sorry but we don't have a lot of time here.
你到底打不打这架直升机?
So what do you wanna do about shooting down this chopper?
-我没法下杀死杰克·鲍尔的命令  -但是你也不能看着萨拉扎逃之夭夭
-I can't give the order to kill Jack Bauer.  -But you can't let Salazar go either.
你是担心萨拉扎的问题么?
Is this Salazar you're worried about?
还是你担心如果杰克·鲍尔还活着 他会泄露我们的密谋
Or you worry that if Jack Bauer lives, he'll talk about our arrangement.
这个是个一针见血的问题 没错 我确实担心那个 即使你不担心
It's a fair question to be blunt, yeah I'm worried about that, even if you're not.
但是你还得考虑国家安全 大卫
But you still have to think about national security David.
萨拉扎不仅是个毒贩子 而且他还和恐怖组织挂钩
I mean Salazar not only runs a drug cartel, but he's connected to terrorist organizations.
而他今天刚刚证明 他有能力在我们本土发动生化攻击
And he has proven to us today that he has the infrastructure to launch a biological attack on our soil.
我们能忍受这种事情再次发生么?
How we can allow him to do that again?
杰克·鲍尔不惜一切阻止这次攻击
Jack Bauer sacrificed everything to prevent that attack.
杰克·鲍尔 自告奋勇的
Jack Bauer volunteered.
杰克·鲍尔 明白这有多危险
Jack Bauer knew the risks,
现在 大卫 你必须当别人在这直升机上 来作出这个决定
now David you have got to make this decision as if that wasn't Jack Bauer on that helicopter.
你得为这个国家着想 大卫
You have to do what's right for this country David.
听着
Listen.
决定权在你手里
This is your call.
是你必须当机立断
But you gonna make it now.
让我和查佩尔说
Get me Chappelle.
离他们抵达停火区只有1分钟了
We now have just over one minute until they reach the no fire zone.
-重复 我们只有...  -等等 少校
-I repeat, we have over just...  -Hold on Major.
-瑞恩·查佩尔?  -我是总统 帕默尔
-Ryan Chappelle?  -This is President Palmer.
为什么你不能让那直升机安全迫降?
Why can't you force down that chopper without firing it?
鲍尔不肯和我们联系 总统先生 他让我们别无选择
Bauer won't communicate with us Mr. President, he's forcing our hand.
我们还有多久?
How much time do we have?
60秒内他就会逃出我们掌心
In 60 seconds he'll be out of reach.
长官?
Sir?
你有我的许可开火
You have my authorization to fire.
是
Yes, Sir.
-少校 把他打下来  -是的 长官
-Major, shoot him down.  -Yes, Sir.
这里是阿尔法 1 呼叫斑马 1和斑马 2
This is Alpha 1 to Zebra 1 and Zebra 2.
执行 你们可以开火 我重复 你们可以开火
Proceed, you have a go, I repeat, you have a go.
收到 阿尔法 1 准备发射
Roger that Alpha 1, preparing to launch.
该死的! 怎么了?
Damn it! What's happening?
他们下命令了
They gave the order.
别 求你了
No please.
能收到么? 我无法瞄准
Do you copy? I don't have a shot.
他改航线了 下降 下降!
He's changing course, get under, get under!
你能射击么?
Do you have a shot?
不行 不行 他知道我在哪儿 他换方向了
Negative, negative. He knows where I am. He knows you're in the way.
-我锁定他了 火箭准备  -你可以开火
-I've got him again. Rocket's engaged.  -You're clear for shot.
目标锁定 我开火了
Target locked. I'm taking the shot.
停火 停火 待命
Hold fire, hold fire, standby.
阿尔法 1 他已经抵达市区 请问我们是否依旧开火?
Alpha 1, he's reaching downtown. Please advise, do we still fire?
不 退后 我重复 不要开火 不要开火
No, stand down, I repeat, do not fire, do not fire.
收到 阿尔法 1 退后
Roger that Alpha 1, standing down
稳住 我们到了
Hold on we're going in.
所有人 改到B计划
All right! Everyone! Fall back to B protocols.
所有地面单位准备
Have all units on the ground and prepared.
我要立刻封锁鲍尔的着陆区域
Wherever Bauer lands, I wanna be on top.
-德斯勒?  -米歇尔怎么了?
-Dessler?  -Michelle, what's going on?
他们没开火了 他已经抵达城市上方
They're not firing. He takes over the city.
你能联系到他了么?
Can you get him on the hailing frequency yet?
克萝伊已经快搞定了
Chloe is getting close.
他降落了 我得挂了
Ok, he's putting it down, I gotta go.
让我和克萝伊说!
Get me to Chloe! Get me to Chloe!
怎么?
Yeah?
克萝伊?
Chloe?
你就不能等几秒蔡斯?
Any seconds left Chase?
没时间了 该死的! 我得在他着陆前联系到他
There is no time damn it! I need to get through before he lands.
搞定了 蔡斯 发送中 好了
I got it Chase, I got it. Patching you through, you're in, go.
杰克 我们找到凯尔 辛格勒
Jack, we found Kyle Singer.
我重复 我们找到凯尔 辛格勒 病毒已经被隔离
I repeat, we found Kyle Singer. The virus is contained.
你没必要这么做
No need for you to doing this.
辛格勒夫妇 我是邓肯医生
Mr. and Ms. Singer, I'm Doctor Duncan.
-你好  -你好
-Hi.  -Hello.
等一下
One more second.
很好 拿着这个
That's good. Get this.
但是我们的治疗手段太有限了
But our options of retrievement are limited.
我不明白
I don't understand.
他还没有发病 为什么没有办法医治他?
If he's not sick yet, why isn't there any way to treat him?
当一个人感染并开始携带病毒
Once someone is exposed and starts incubating the virus,
我们就无能为力了
there is nothing we can do.
那么 他大概还有多久?
So, how long does he have?
实验报告还没有出来
The lab tests haven't come back yet,
-一旦我们有了更多...  -求您了! 我只是想知道大概多久
-once we do we'll have a more...  -Please! Just give me some idea.
几小时 一天都不到
Hours, not days.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-我们能见见他么?  -当然
-Can we see him?  -Of course.
-来吧 亲爱的 -我做不到! 我做不到!
-Come on honey.  -I can't! I can't!
海伦 他需要知道我们并不生他的气
Hey, Helen he needs to know that we're not angry with him.
凯尔? 你的父母想和你谈谈
Kyle? Your parents would like to speak with you.
他们可以从对讲机里听到你
They can hear you through the intercom.
你们随意 我在外面等着
Take your time, I'll be just outside.
-医生告诉我们全部了  -但是也许是他们搞错了!
-The doctor told us everything.  -But maybe they're wrong!
也许情况并没有他们想象的这么糟糕
Maybe it isn't as bad as they think.
他们并没有搞错
They're not wrong.
我是罪有应得
I deserve what I'm getting.
别这样 你所应得的是一个能待你更好的父亲
Don't say that, all you deserve is a father who could do better for you,
这样你就不用因为我的无能而出去挣钱
so you wouldn't have to go and get money and bring it home because I couldn't.
我对不起你 凯尔 我真的对不起你
I'm sorry, Kyle, I'm so sorry.
我爱你
I love you.
你总是为我操心
You've always taking care of me.
而我却...
Now I've never...
而我却从来没有告诉过你
now I've never told you this.
你让我感到安心
But you made me feel safe.
即使现在...
Even now...
你使我感到安心
you make me feel safe.
你是无可挑剔的 爸
You did the best you could dad.
我要死了
I will die.
-我要死了  -别
-I will die.  -No, no.
我是反恐局的埃德蒙兹 谁看见他了?
Edmunds, CTU, anybody seen him.
目击者看见你的嫌疑犯5分钟前跑进地铁站
Witnesses saw your suspects run down at to the station over 5 minutes ago.
-有几辆地铁离开了?  -两辆
-How many trains have left?  -Two.
一辆在向东10街区的地方停了一站
One made a stop 10 blocks east of here.
我们有警官正在搜索那个区域
We got officers searching that area.
我们在隧道里拦下另一辆 警察正在搜索
We stopped another train in the tunnel, they're searching it now.
杰克不会让自己被拦在一辆地铁里
Jack's not gonna let himself be trapped in a train.
你认为他在隧道里
You think he's still down the tunnel.
反恐局 鲍尔?
CTU, Bauer?
金 我要整个潘兴广场地铁站的设计图
Kim I need the entire schematic of the Pershing Square station.
怎么了蔡斯?
What's going on Chase?
你父亲在我联系上他之前就离开了直升机 现在正和萨拉扎逃亡中
Your dad got out of the Chopper before I can tell about Kyle Singer, he and Salazar are on the run.
等下 我找到图纸了
Hang on, ok I've got the schematics.
从这里到格朗一共有多少隧道紧急出口
How many tunnels emergency access are their between here and Grant.
嗯
Heuuu?
-金?  -我在找
-Kim?  -I'm looking.
快点 我们得行动
Come on, let's go.
只有一个 在小巷里
There is one, in the alley.
在第6街的西南角
Just off 6th street south-west corner.
离这里多远?
How far is that from here?
一个街区 但是那儿都是单行道 你最好徒步过去
One block, but they are one ways so you'll be better off on foot.
好 我会再联系
Ok, I'll get back to you.
喂! 到底要不要我们帮忙?
Hey! Are we coordinating with you guys or not?
米歇尔 我刚刚和蔡斯 通过话 他正在地铁站
Michelle, I just get off the phone with Chase, he's at the metro station.
-他有什么事?  -找有关地铁的信息
-What did he want?  -Information about the subways.
把你提供给他的给其它的员工也备一份
Whatever you gave him, copy to all other agents.
-我已经照办了  -很好
-I did.  -Good.
他们不会使用极端手段 对吧?
They know not to use lethal force, right?
命令没有变
Mandate is the same.
不惜一切阻止萨拉扎
Stop Salazar by any means necessary.
但由于他们在地上 他们也许可以避免伤害你父亲
But now that they're on the ground, they can probably do that without harming your father.
说的是
Right.
德斯勒?
Dessler?
米歇尔 我是蔡斯 杰克从隧道的维修通道逃离了
Michelle, it's Chase, Jack got out of a tunnel to a maintenance access of mission
位于900街区 你需要重新安排这个地区的人手分布
the 900 block, you need to redeploy all your people this area.
-方圆10街区内全部封锁  -我明白了
-seal off a 10-block radius.  -I'm on it.
上车
Come on, get in.
总统的临时退出辩论实在是太恰到好处了
The exit of the President did come at a critical time of the debate
或者说是经过深思熟虑的? 双方的支持者
and even pondered?? on both side of the isle
都认为这很不同寻常
are speculating that it is quite odd, to say the least,
好 我会
Yeah, I will.
我会转告他 谢谢
I will tell him, thanks.
是反恐局打来的
It was CTU.
他们依旧没有找到鲍尔或萨拉扎
They still haven't found Bauer or Salazar.
警局正被派到直升机着陆点周围
LAPD is placing a perimeter area where the Chopper landed.
希望他们能顺利的被找到
Hopefully they'll be picked up without an incident.
希望
Yeah.
是啊 其实让鲍尔溜掉的可能性更大
Yeah, it's probably more likely that Bauer sneaked through.
大卫 听着
David, listen.
你现在得把他的安危暂时忘掉
You gonna have to stop thinking about his welfare for the moment.
鲍尔帮萨拉扎越狱的事情让媒体知道了
That Bauer breaking Salazar out of prison has already leaked to the press.
现在你不得不做的 是去解释这就是为什么你中止辩论
Now you gonna have to go out there, and explain to them that's why you ended this debate.
然后公开谴责鲍尔的所作所为
And then explicitly denounce what Bauer did.
就是说 杰克不顾生命危险拯救国家 我们却对他弃之不顾
So Jack puts his life on the line to stop the fire so we hang him out dry.
大卫 我们不能让任何人知道 是我们默许了他的行动.
David we cannot allow anyone to know that we sanctionned what he did.
那样对于你和你内阁的损失将是无可挽回
That would do irreparable damage to you, to the office.
你知道我说的是事实
Now you know what I'm saying is true.
我对此很抱歉 但是你不能帮他
No sorry but you gonna have to let him go.
你在给谁打电话?
Who are you calling?
飞行员
The pilot.
上次的电话里 你兄弟给了FBI的联系方式
Your brother gave the FBI contact instructions in his last call,
他的飞机正准备接你
he's got a plane circling waiting to pick you up.
所以反恐局知道那架飞机 那会不会造成问题?
So CTU knows about the plane. Would that be a problem?
很快就不会了
Not for a long.
喂?
Yes?
喂 我是杰克·鲍尔 我救出了萨拉扎
Yes, this is Jack Bauer, I've got Salazar.
我用的是保密手机: 7 1 1 * 6 5 5 9
I'm on a secure cell: 7, 1, 1, *, 6, 5, 5, 9.
调整一下你的频率 然后给我回电
Reconfigure your frequency and call me back.
-调整完毕  -很好
-I get confirmation.  -That's right.
-这事属实么?  -是的
-Is this the real thing?  -Yes.
他救出了萨拉扎 给他回电安排会头
Yes it is, he's got Salazar, call him back and make arrangements.
你在反恐局监听
And you'll buffer from CTU.
就绪 打给他
It's handled.
喂?
Yeah?
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
费格奥 2700 街区 我们正在向南开
2700 block of Figerow. We're heading south.
明白
All right,
最安全的着陆点是 圣玛格丽塔 你知道那是哪儿么?
the closest safe airstrip is Santa Margarita. Do you know where that is?
知道 我10分钟内会赶到那里
Yeah, I can get there in about 10 minutes.
你果然是最棒的 杰克
You really are the best Jack.
当你潜伏在我们之中时 我从来不曾想到你是个特工
When you were down there with us I had no idea your were an agent.
我们接受了你
We accepted you.
你没有吸毒的必要
You didn't have to put the needle in your arm.
你是为了其他目的才这么做的
You did that for other reasons.
和所有渣滓一样 为了止痛
Same reason as all junkies, to kill the pain.
你的痛处是什么 杰克?
What's your pain Jack?
你试图通过吸毒忘却的是什么?
What does the needle make go away?
记得通知局里 叫他们的人撤出唐尼
Make sure to call Division, tell them that they need to move their men out of Downey.
-还是派到那里?  -是的 我们要把人手全派到市中心
-Same place?  -Yeah, we need everyone downtown.
米歇尔 林策医生在三号线等你
Michelle Dr. Linzer on line 3.
这要一会 行么?
It will take a few minutes, is that all right?
-行 解决后通知我  -明白
-Yeah call me back with confirmation.  -All right.
-喂 医生?  -您丈夫的手术已经完成
-Yeah Doctor? -Well, your husband is out of surgery.
他怎么样?
How is he?
没有神经损伤 只是血管受伤
Their was no nerve damaged, the injury was entirely vascular.
是最好结果 对么?
It's what we're hoping for, right?
对
Yes.
他会痊愈
He should recover fully.
谢天谢地!
Thank God!
现在 他正在手术后休息 1个小时内应该会醒来
Now, he is going in a post-op now so he should be awake in the next hour or so.
我会去的
I'll be there.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢您 医生
Thank you Doctor.
是医院打来的
It was the hospital.
托尼没事了
Tony is gonna be ok.
这是好消息
That's good news.
谢谢 瑞恩
Thank you Ryan.
有任何INS的消息么?
Have you heard back from INS?
是的 我们发出了警报
Yeah we send out an alert.
从巴哈马到新墨西哥都有我们的人手
And we cover from Baha to New-Mexico.
地方机场呢?
How about local airfields?
我们尽量让机场禁用 但
We're trying to shutdown everything we can but,
航空局并不是很合作
we're getting a little bogged down with the FAA.
让盖尔对地方航线进行监视分析
Have Gael run a pattern analysis on local air traffic,
也许我们能找到异常
we may come up with an anomaly.
我已经安排的
It's a good idea.
-考夫曼?  -亚当 盖尔呢?
-Kaufman?  -Adam, where's Gael?
在技术1部
Hmmmm, Tech. 1.
金和我正要下去 有什么要我转告他的?
Kim and I are just about to head down there, do you need me to tell him something?
-不用 叫他过来就行  -好
-No, just send him over to my office  -Ok.
-我会转告的  -谢谢
-I'll let him know.  -Thanks.
你一旦升空 我就挂线
Once you get back in the air I'll be offline.
你每隔15分钟搜索一次频率 我会用22.7频率联系你
You comute your frequency every 15 minutes, I'll pick you up in 22.7.
明白
Roger that.
我会回电
I'll get back to you.
从11点起系统就没有更新过了
So everything on the system hasn't been updated since 11 am.
你从那时开始就好
So that's where you should start.
好
Ok.
盖尔?
Gael?
米歇尔要你去她办公室
Michelle needs to see you in her office.
知道了
Ok.
-你可以用这里的机器  -好
-You can use the station right here.  -Great.
你们在忙什么?
What are you doing?
只是把登记更新一下 今天事发后 一切都被耽搁了
Ah, bringing the logs back up to date, we got really behind when everything hit the fan today.
做这个我比她有经验
I can do that a lot faster than she can.
不 米歇尔要你马上过去
No, Michelle needs to see you now.
好了
Ok.
-你可以开始了  -好极了
-You're all set.  -Great.
-过会见  -好
-See you in a bit.  -Yeah.
阁下?
Sir?
-能稍等一下么?  -好
-Can you give me a moment?  -Yeah.
把这两段换一下
Have these 2 paragraphs inverted.
安排秘书早上和我见面
And have the secretary meet me in the morning.
-明白了么?  -是 长官
-All right?  -Yes sir.
一切还好么?
Is everything ok?
不 我们得当机立断 解决那些我之前没能在台上解决的问题
No we had to make some fast choices and I couldn't do that while I was on stage.
不过 对
Yes.
-现在一切都好了  -你确定?
-Everything is ok now.  -Are you sure?
这只是善后处理
This is just damage control.
大卫 我很抱歉 我只是...
David I'm sorry, I just...
我不敢相信基勒还在竞选辩论时散布那些谎言
I still can't believe Keeler would repeat those lies in a national debate.
你不需要为任何事道歉
You don't have to apologize for anything.
你没有他们那么低级
You didn't sink to their level.
而且从长远来看
And in the long run,
值得这么做
it's gonna pay off.
我相信你是对的
I hope you're right.
但我更担心你
But I'm more concerned about you.
你是因我才被卷进来
You've only been brought into this because of me.
我没事
I'm fine.
我相信
Yes, you are.
大卫 杰瑞 安排一个新闻招待会
David, Jerry has scheduled a press conference.
他们今晚想要一个解释
They're expecting a statement this evening.
好吧
Fine.
我们得针对基勒对于安妮的指责作出回复
We've got to get right on a response to Keeler's accusation about Anne.
简报上怎么说?
What did the quick post tell us?
老实告诉你 我们处境不乐观
Well I'm not gonna lie to you. We got hit hard.
骑墙观望的选民很可能转而支持基勒
Voters who are on a fence may have just fall into Keeler's camp.
但是一旦他们发现泰德在撒谎 就会知道这是无稽之谈
But that is ridiculous once they'll find out that Ted was lying.
但他们怎么会知道 安妮?
But how are they supposed to do that Anne?
这一切都是人云亦云 这就是政治
I mean it's he said, she said, see this is politics,
并不像治病 所以麻烦你别掺和进来
it's not medicine, so do me a favor and stay out of it.
别掺和进来? 我已经身在其中了!
Stay out of it? I am it!
够了
That's enough.
韦恩 你耐心点
Wayne, you gonna have to be patient.
安妮不会离开这里 我们也不改变政策
Anne's not going anywhere, and we are not changing our strategy.
-大卫 我们真的...  -现在 你得叫我总统先生
-David we really...  -Right now, it's Mr. President.
是 总统先生
Yes, Sir. Mr. President.
虽然我并不喜欢他说教的态度
I may not agree with his bedside manner,
但是我想他说得没错
but I think he's right.
你现在不需要这样
You don't need this right now.
你在说什么?
Now, what are you saying?
我觉得我们应该等到选举后再交往
I think we should put our relationship on hold until after the election.
等等 首先
Wow, wow, first of all,
这于事无补
that won't resolve anything,
其次 我需要你
and second of all, I need you.
那我哪儿也不去
Then I'm right here.
这才是我的爱人
That's my lady.
等下
Wait a minute.
这怎么可能?
How can that be?
-这些结果有经复查么?  -已经查了3次了 医生
-Have we rechecked these results?  -3 times Doctor.
-你肯定?  -很肯定
-You're sure?  -Very sure.
好了 多谢
Ok, thanks.
帮我给反恐局的查佩尔打电话 转给我手机
Yeah, get me Chappelle at CTU, put him through to my cell.
怎么了?
What's going on?
你的血液中没有病毒的痕迹
There is no trace of the virus in your blood.
什么?
What?
我们复查了好几遍
We've rerun the tests several times,
并在另一个实验室里复核过
and have them double checked in another lab.
你没被感染
You're clean.
上帝啊!
Ohh! My God!
-邓肯?  -妮可? 我是查佩尔
-Duncan?  -Nicole? Chappelle.
凯尔 辛格勒的检验报告为阴性
Kyle Singer's tests came back negative.
这怎么可能?
How is that possible?
唯一的解释是 他从来没有被感染过
It's only possible if he was never infected.
你是在说这个病毒威胁是空穴来风?
So you're telling me this whole virus scare was a bluff?
我可不会这么说
Hard enough I'd say that.
今天早上他们留下的那具尸体肯定是被感染的
That dead body they dropped off this morning, was definitely infected.
那他们为什么没有感染那个孩子?
Then why wouldn't have infected the boy?
这到底怎么回事?
What the hell is going on here?
我怎么知道
I don't know, you tell me.
怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
你把我送到这儿 我还会让你走吗?
You didn't think I was gonna let you just deliver me and leave, did you?
让他下车
Get him off.
拉姆!
Ramon!
到底怎么回事 拉姆?
What the hell is going on Ramon?
-多谢帮忙 杰克  -拉姆!
-Thanks for the ride Jack.  -Ramon!
赫克托要他跟我们走
Hector said to bring him back,
活着
alive.
好吧
Fine.
我们走
Let's go.
亚当!
Adam!
亚当 这里出事了
Adam, there is something seriously wrong.
我刚想起来
I've just remembered.
我没关那个文件夹
I forgot to close that file.